Eui-ju!
CHAPTER 26: YOU'RE AN OUTLIER
Are you in pain, miss?
Are you Ms. Yeo's guardian?
Yes.
How long has she been sweating like this?
-About 30 minutes. -Does she often suffer abdominal pain?
-I'm not sure. -Okay.
Will you please wait in the waiting room?
Is it serious?
-Just wait for now. -All right.
Doctor, it's an emergency.
Let me check you over.
It hurts.
-It hurts here? -Yes.
What about here? Does it hurt a lot?
Let's take her to the emergency treatment room.
Let's go.
EMERGENCY ROOM ENTRY RESTRICTIONS
Anyone going in there falls under one of just two categories.
It must be serious.
The poor thing.
"Serious"?
HANA UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Is Yeo Eui-ju's guardian here?
Yes, that's me.
Mr. Ga.
What am I going to do now, Mr. Ga?
I should've known.
I did wonder about
why I've lost my appetite and been suffering from indigestion.
I saw a case like mine on TV.
Acute leukemia.
Even people who appear healthy get struck down like this.
But if you collapse suddenly like this, it means you don't have long to live.
I'm…
I'm only 18 years old.
When I became an adult,
I wanted to buy an R-rated novel in my own name
and load my account up with 100,000 won at a time and read whatever I wanted.
Mr. Ga.
I…
I have a bad feeling about this.
I really think…
Are you feeling better?
What's wrong with her?
Here you are, doctor.
Oh, dear.
All right. Let's take a look at your X-ray together.
You can see here. It's been building up for quite a while.
Not good at all.
Why didn't you come in sooner?
Mr. Ga, what am I going to do?
Oh, my.
It's okay. It won't be that serious.
Mr. Ga, I don't want to die.
Don't worry. Hush now.
-What do I do? -They can treat you.
Please call my mom.
They can treat you. You will be fine!
Is it a serious illness?
She had constipation.
Sorry?
But…
Can constipation cause you to pass out?
Shouldn't you run more tests?
She was full to bursting.
All the white you see here is stool.
We gave her an enema.
And this is how you look now.
Isn't that nice and clean?
When you get home,
why don't you try weighing yourself?
You're free to leave.
Please just leave, Mr. Ga.
I'll make my own way home.
Please just leave without another word.
Please.
Why aren't you going?
Please just leave.
Right now.
I will never get…
how you…
always manage…
to prove yourself to be an outlier.
I'm off.
Shall I just transfer?
Oh, my.
Eui-ju!
-Where is she? -Eui-ju!
-Eui-ju! -Eui-ju!
-Eui-ju! -I'm fine.
-Eui-ju! -Does it hurt a lot?
Mom, I want to transfer.
Transfer?
EPISODE 8
Why do you think Woo-su changed his mind about filming?
He must have been blackmailed.
Do you know how scary the principal is?
Her expression can change in an instant.
He's not the type to give in to blackmail.
-Right. -Sure.
-Yeah. -You got that right.
What has she got on him?
He's home. You'd better apologize properly.
Okay already.
You're late. You haven't had dinner yet?
I'll go get some rice. You can get the soup.
Great work today.
Is that it?
Didn't you have something to say to him?
I'm sorry about earlier.
About what, exactly?
Dude, can't you just accept my apology?
Well.
You know.
I'm sorry that I went behind your back
to have you filmed when I knew you hated it
and brushed off your past trauma like it was nothing.
At least you know.
What about cutlery?
Right. I'll get it.
You're so cool.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
I won't call you fruit bat for the next month.
Can you just not call me that at all?
-What do you think? -You totally can, glasses monkey!
-Jeez, you fruit bat. -Hey!
Did you hear that? He just did it!
He said he wouldn't!
I never pinky-promised.
I'm not eating anymore.
-Why the heck am I a fruit bat? -Suit yourself.
I thought I was done with embarrassing myself.
Eui-ju!
So broad,
so warm…
and so cozy.
According to a study on constipation in teens
and related factors,
the top three causes of constipation are
low levels of physical activity at 43%, excessive instant food intake at 24.6%,
and irregular sleep patterns at 16%.
I assume these contributed to the unfortunate incident yesterday.
I'll keep that in mind.
Thank you for yesterday.
I'm not religious, but it was a weird feeling.
I bestowed grace upon the student who betrayed me.
How backed up were you that you had to go to the ER?
It's because you don't drink enough water.
Your poop gets hard like stones and won't come out.
What? Wait, no.
Are you okay, Eui-ju?
I hear you went to the ER.
How could you hold it in until it got that bad?
You're definitely a bit slow.
Oh, and thanks for yesterday.
Mr. Noh.
What was that about yesterday? You said you knew something.
What?
You said you knew my secret.
What would I know?
I can totally see the change.
You're looking a lot better today.
What the heck?
Did he trick me?
So the math teacher hasn't spilled the beans about my novel?
Hey, Eui-ju! Going to the ER with constipation?
That's no big deal!
There's no need to feel embarrassed!
Just make sure you poop properly!
You got this, Eui-ju!
Constipation is no joke!
All right, fine. See you!
-Oh A-rin. -Here.
CHAPTER 27: LIKE A CAT, LITTLE BY LITTLE
-Choi Yu-mi. -Here.
-Yeo Eui-ju. -Here.
-Choi Go-ya. -Here.
Choi Ji-a.
-Hong Su-min. -Here.
-Jeon Chae-won. -Here.
-Im Su-yeon. -Here.
-Jenny. -Here.
Give it your all in class today. Have a good one.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
Eui-ju, come with me.
Why isn't Ji-a here?
I don't know.
When I asked about Ji-a on day one, you were the only one who answered.
Want to guess how I interpreted it?
I thought that with your help, she might feel more positive about school.
She might even change. That made me trust you.
I want you to step up your game and try to help her.
Let's say you know someone is waiting for you at school.
Even if you hated it,
you'd still drag yourself here, wouldn't you?
The thing is, the way I see it,
Ji-a is not the kind of girl you can just go up to.
What I mean is, she's just like a cat.
You have to creep up to her cautiously, little by little.
Try that, then.
But you're getting four demerits today.
Are you going to betray my trust?
No, sir.
What on earth…
Damn you, Ji-a.
Ji-a's absent again.
Tell me about it.
By the way, why is she always by herself?
I'm not sure.
Some people just prefer keeping themselves to themselves.
Maybe she's one.
To be honest, I find her a bit scary.
Feels like things will kick off if I rub her the wrong way.
Come on, she's not much of a talker, but she's not like that.
She was in my class in tenth grade.
I remember she always picked up a chalk that fell on the floor.
Oh, and whereas other kids found it a pain to do the recycling,
she would stay behind alone to take care of it.
So…
There are people who favor actions rather than words.
I think that's her style.
Here she is now.
There you are.
You could've come earlier.
Why were you late today?
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
-Good morning. -Good morning.
Let's turn to page 280.
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir.
We're celebrating the literature month with a poetry and art exhibition.
Each class has to select a representative.
Does anyone want to try writing a poem?
Sir, Eui-ju's your girl.
She's an amazing writer.
Yeah, she's always working on some project.
She even won a creative writing prize last year.
Really? Then she can be your class representative.
Is that okay, Eui-ju?
Okay, I'll do it.
Sir, can Go-ya help out by drawing?
Sounds great.
Is that okay, Go-ya?
Sure, anything I can do to help.
Then class two will be represented by Yeo Eui-ju and Choi Go-ya.
Looking forward to it.
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir. We'll do our best.
Are you in detention for demerits?
Yes, sir.
I never know when I might get more.
So I have to work them off.
Did you have lunch?
Yes. How about you, sir?
I did too.
Eui-ju.
Yes?
Mr. Ga knows you weren't filming him the other day.
Really?
Then why is he being so hard on me?
It must be because of his glasses.
His glasses?
Yes.
I had his glasses
back when he lost them.
You had them?
Yes.
Didn't he tell you?
He never said anything.
What the heck?
I thought he would've trashed me to his friends for throwing them out.
Anyhow, I don't think he's holding a grudge against you.
So don't get too upset.
Okay. Thanks for looking out for me.
I think it's so cool you're a published writer.
It's nothing.
I've just enjoyed writing poetry since middle school.
I started off casually like I was writing in a diary,
putting into words the emotions I couldn't keep bottled up.
I had a fair share of failures with the Spring Literary Contest
until a literary magazine luckily picked up my piece.
Of course, I still doubt myself even now,
wondering if my writing is good enough.
Still,
eventually, I realized that writing is all about putting my heart into it.
To tell the truth,
I've written several novels.
Really?
That's so cool.
Not at all.
Sir, how can I write a really great novel?
Make sure each character has their own voice.
I think that's important.
Each character should have their own voice?
Yes.
That's so profound.
Now, I'm really looking forward to your submission.
Oh, come on.
You went to the snack bar?
Yeah.
I would've gone with you.
Thank you.
Where have you been?
Huh? I had a chat with Mr. Yoon.
Hey, he's so amazing.
He started writing poems in middle school.
He had no luck with Spring Literary Contests,
but he got his big break through another channel.
I'll do my best with the piece for our exhibition.
That way, your brilliant picture will shine.
We'll show everyone
what an amazing artist you are.
Shoot, I'm so nervous.
Should we work on a title first?
No.
CHAPTER 28: I'M GOING TO TRY TO UNDERSTAND IRRATIONAL NUMBERS
FILES FOR MR. GA REAL FILES
Okay.
FILES FOR MR. GA
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
WOO-SUUUUUUUU
This won't do.
I'm skipping this, dang it.
Let's move on for now.
I'm not feeling it.
REAL FILES
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
JUST THEN, SOMEONE GRABBED…
Why haven't you come to my place lately?
YOON'S EYES WIDEN IN SURPRISE. IT'S SI-ON
I can't.
No, I don't want to.
Can you pass discrete math by yourself?
You'll flunk without my help.
I'll figure it out by myself.
I'll pay you.
What?
You need money.
I'll pay you to come to my house.
Isn't that why you go to Tae-ha's?
It's not like that.
Yes, it is.
How is that punk any different from me?
Tae-ha is nothing like you.
And how exactly is he different?
Ultimately, he's also using money to make you do what he wants.
You're poor, so instead of money, you'll have to find another way to repay me.
That ten million won.
Pay me back properly.
Fine, take it out on me.
Go ahead, keep your pride.
But in the end, you'll take it.
I'm curious how much your pride is worth.
Why are you going this far?
Do you have to bring me down like this?
Do I seem like a pushover to you?
Don't waste your breath and come up with a number.
You're going to regret this.
You're really going to regret this.
No.
I'll never regret it.
Not even to my dying day.
END OF EPISODE 5
"Save."
FILES FOR MR. GA
You can do it.
Okay, Eui-ju?
You've got this.
I can't seem to stop yawning.
I need to get home and crash.
You'd need to eat first.
What are we going to eat?
No idea. I'll have to think about it.
Something crispy and warm.
-Jeez, you're so fussy. -Crispy!
We've got some curry.
-Curry? -Yeah, from the other day.
You guys go ahead.
-Where are you going? -Library.
He's always off to the library.
Be home in time for dinner!
Does the school library have anything at his level?
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
From now on,
I'll be your personal bitch.
This isn't like you.
Oh yeah?
EPISODE 5, FOR MR. GA
What am I like, then?
You never cared about me.
You only did a 180 after I became close to Tae-ha.
Are you jealous or something?
Jealous?
Me? Jealous?
Damn right I am!
All that icy treatment was just an act
to hide how I felt about you.
But seeing you with Tae-ha is driving me crazy.
It's too late.
Get it together, Yoon!
Without me, there's no one left for you.
You have no other choice.
Without me,
you've got nothing!
END OF EPISODE 5
What's the matter, Mr. Ga?
Don't you like it?
I wrote him as an obsessive top.
What doesn't he like about it?
Jeez, he still has his glasses taped up.
What are you staring at?
I was wondering if you'd got new glasses.
My order's not ready yet.
They must be really expensive.
I'm sorry I couldn't buy them for you.
Are you sorry for what happened?
Of course.
What about giving up on math?
That too.
Write how you want to.
Sorry?
Write your own version, not what I tell you.
Really?
That's amazing.
Is this for real?
To tell the truth, after you caught me,
I thought it was game over.
I figured that was it for me.
Why are you allowing me to write again?
To Pythagoras, the square root of two was an abnormal number.
Sorry?
What's that got to do with it?
Back then, the only numbers they could calculate were natural numbers.
Anything that couldn't be expressed as a fraction was considered irrational.
Such numbers were to be rejected and not even thought of.
I get why the Pythagoreans were shaken.
Hippasus, who discovered the square root of two,
died in suspicious circumstances.
They killed him over that?
No one knows who killed him. It's just a theory.
Wow, Pythagoras was scary.
What do irrational numbers really mean?
It's "irrational" numbers, right?
I believe that things that appear irrational or illogical
still deserve our time and attention.
I won't repeat Pythagoras's mistake and dismiss something
just because it seems irrational.
Could you put that in layman's terms?
I'm going to try to understand irrational numbers.
Fangirling used to be my only joy in life.
-But now… -Are you okay?
The fact he keeps cropping up in my mind…
It makes me mad.
-I don't want to think about him. -Let's go.
I shouldn't think about him,
but I can't help myself.
You're into someone, but you don't want to admit it.
You're in denial.
No matter how much you deny it, you're already into him.
No. No way.
I shouldn't even like him,
and I just can't.
The guy you like isn't Mr. Jung, is it?
They've gotten really close.
Subtitle: Paul Carver